<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rui Lei</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rui Lei</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 19:53:33 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>convert PowerPoint Presentation video to images and captions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/convert-powerpoint-presentation-video-to-images-and-captions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/convert-powerpoint-presentation-video-to-images-and-captions/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a great idea: this tool &amp;ldquo;PPT Presentation Video to Transcript + Images&amp;rdquo; could be used to generate high-quality datasets!&#xA;The Flamingo dataset contains video texts and web multimodal texts. However, it consists of short videos, averaging only 22 seconds, so it definitely can&amp;rsquo;t achieve fine-grained information. It&amp;rsquo;s likely a combination of video and video descriptions. Today, I can do it! b3aca2da675d67feb7e3d0977cb1381a&#xA;Here are the key steps:&#xA;Extract keyframes from the video to create a list of PPT images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Render Math With Mathjax</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/math/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 19:53:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/math/</guid>
      <description>Mathjax Math equations can be rendered using Mathjax syntax with AMS symbol support.&#xA;Optionally enable this on a per-page basis by adding mathjax: true to your frontmatter.&#xA;Then, use $$ ... $$ on a line by itself to render a block equation:&#xA;$$ | Pr_{x \leftarrow P_{1}} [A(x) = 1] - Pr_{x \leftarrow P_{2}} [A(x) = 1] | &amp;lt; \text{negligible} $$&#xA;The raw version is:&#xA;$$ | Pr_{x \leftarrow P_{1}} [A(x) = 1] - Pr_{x \leftarrow P_{2}} [A(x) = 1] | &amp;lt; \text{negligible} $$ Write in-line equations with \\( .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 18:35:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 23:29:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>Paragraph Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo. Aque venitatiusda cum, voluptionse latur sitiae dolessi aut parist aut dollo enim qui voluptate ma dolestendit peritin re plis aut quas inctum laceat est volestemque commosa as cus endigna tectur, offic to cor sequas etum rerum idem sintibus eiur? Quianimin porecus evelectur, cum que nis nust voloribus ratem aut omnimi, sitatur? Quiatem. Nam, omnis sum am facea corem alique molestrunt et eos evelece arcillit ut aut eos eos nus, sin conecerem erum fuga.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 22:53:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways. :zap:&#xA;Emoji Support The emojify function can be called directly in templates or Inline Shortcodes.&#xA;To enable emoji globally, set enableEmoji to true in your site’s configuration and then you can type emoji shorthand codes directly in content files; e.g.&#xA;The Emoji cheat sheet is a useful reference for emoji shorthand codes.&#xA;N.B. The above steps enable Unicode Standard emoji characters and sequences in Hugo, however the rendering of these glyphs depends on the browser and the platform.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
